(Sheldon:)I wish you could all be inside my head.
(Sheldon:)The conversation is sparkling.
(Sheldon:)Fine, I'll tell you.
(Sheldon:)A lichen is an organism made up
of two separate species, fungi and algae.
(Sheldon:)If you could merge with another species,
what species would you pick and why?
(Sheldon:)Hint, there is a right answer.
(Sheldon:)None of you will get it.
Okay. Um, l'd pick swan
because, uh, the resuIting hybrid...
(Raj:)...would have the advanced
industrial civilization of a human...
(Raj:)...and the long, graceful neck
l've always dreamed of having.
(Sheldon:)Wrong. Leonard?
(Leonard:)Horse. But mostly just for the height.
(Leonard:)A little bit for the genital girth.